they won't let us live anymore well this is a war again
они не дадут жить уже ну это опять война
like it will drag on again further and further
типа затянется опять дальше будет дальше
people will die right It's better
будут люди погибать правильно Так лучше
that they don't die it's better that Russia
чтобы не погибали лучше чтобы Россия
gives Donetsk back Lugansk to Ukraine everything will
отдала Донецк Луганск назад Украине всё
never be given back never will be given back Well so it
никогда не отдадут никогда не отдаст Ну
turns out Putin doesn't want peace
так вот получается Путин не хочет мира
yes and here people don't even want to be with Ukraine
да а здесь люди даже не хотят с Украиной
anymore
уже
Hello Hello
Привет Привет ты
where are you from Lugansk I understand
откуда Луганск поня
in Lugansk I understood How old are you
г в Луганске понял Сколько тебе
40 I understood well I wonder or were you 18
лет 40 понял ну интересно или было 18
when there was
когда Был
Maidan then there was Well you were 18 when there was
Майдан значит был Ну было 18 когда Был
Maidan there that wife cooks food there's
Майдан там что жена Кушать готовит звук
such a sound I didn't understand how it is with you
такой у меня не понял как там у вас
now in Lugansk It's
сейчас в Луганске
calm Yes normally We live and rejoice
спокойно Да нормально Живём радуемся
yes Everything is good everything we live and rejoice I understood
да Всё хорошо всё живём радуемся понял
you were released there everything is
вас там освободили уже всё
calm already Well for a long time now how much is the
спокойно Ну давно уже сколько сейчас
salary in
зарплата в
Lugansk now it's different
Луганске по-разному
with
с
how much where to buy weight Well here how much I wo
сколько где поку веси Ну вот у вас
n't tell you
сколько много не буду шать
why is this classified information
почему это секретная информация
And what do you
А кем ты
work as this is also classified information
работаешь это тоже секретная информация
and what are you even
а о чём ты вообще тут
talking about here about lives about
говоришь о жизнях о
people I understood why are you talking about my profession
людях понял зачем говорите мою профессию
my salaries about life people like  do you think
мои заплаты о жизни люди как считаешь
why Putin attacked
почему Путин напал на
Ukraine
Украину потому
because the heads of the DPR and LPR asked for protection Well, damn,
что главы ДНР лнр попросили защи Ну блин
we understand that the DPR It was a Russian
мы понимаем что ДНР Это был русский
project there was no DPR and LPR there were
проект никакого ДНР лнр не было были
Russian leaders, Russian instructors,
русские руководители русские инструктора
everything is there or do you want to say that the
всё там или ты хочешь сказать что
huge Ukrainian army was held back by
огромную украинскую армию сдерживали
miners with sticks what are you saying
шахтёры с палками что ты рассказываешь
Well, not exactly like that Well, there were Russian
Ну не совсем так Ну были же российские
troops in 2014, no one
войска четырнадцатого года уже никто
even
даже не
hides it No, there weren't, everything helped, but there
скрывает Нет не было все помогало но не
weren't Well, like Wagner Wagner himself stated
было Ну как Вагнер Вагнер сам заявлял
that they recaptured the Lugansk support in 2014
что Луганский опор в 14м году они
Well, Vakh is a private
Ну Вах - Это частная
company, it's a state-owned one,
компания это государственная
no Vanya, I don't think Wagner Even now,
не Ваня не считаю Вагнер Даже сейчас
when Who is financing Who is financing Who is financing Who is financing Wagner
когда Кем финансируется Кем
financed Prigozhin
финансируется финансировал Пригожин
Prigozhin where did he get the money from Well, from those
Пригожин откуда деньги брал Ну от тех
people who hired them, I understand, okay,
людей кто их во нанимал понял ладно
listen, how are you doing now,
слушай Как там у вас вообще сейчас
factories, ships are developing in Lugansk
заводы пароходы развиваются в Луганске
Yes, of course, everything is
Да конечно всё
working, young people come to Lugansk To
работает молодёжь приезжает в Луганск
study there from
Учиться там с
Rostov, honestly, I  I can't say the beginning of this topic
Ростова честно я нач этой темы не могу
Well, somehow I do
сказать Ну я как-то
n't have a name there By the way, do
там нету именя там у вас Кстати знако у
you know many acquaintances who
вас на сво много знакомых есть
died Yes, there are
погибших Да
enough And why are there so many dead
хватает А почему их так много погибших
Well, because this is a war, but there are
Ну пото что это война а вот россиян
few Russians That is, I have a feeling
немного То есть у меня такое ощущение
that the Russians are driving the Donetsk and Lugansk
что россияне донецких и луганских
guys like
пацанов гонят как
meat Well, why are they all dying Well, the Muscovites are
мясо Ну помирают все почему Ну москвичи
not dying and Akhmat is not dying
не помирают и Ахмат не помирает
I don't really follow like who of them is there, there are
я как-то не слежу типа кто там из них
many Muscovites or not This is a war
москви много Это война
and from that side as from this
и с той как с этой
side Listen, what do you think, like, do
стороны Слушай а как ты считаешь типа ну
you want peace so that the guys don't die
ты хочешь мира чтобы пацаны не погибали
Well, of course, if for example they
коне Ну конечно если например
agree that Putin gives Crimea to Donetsk to
договорятся что Путин отдаёт Крым Донецк
Lugansk to Ukraine and the war ends, do you
луганску Украине и война заканчивается
want that Well, no, I'll
хочешь такого Ну нет помирать пацаны
stop dying, guys, that will never happen No,
перестану это никогда такого не будет Не
but if it happens, so that it doesn't matter, guys
ну а если будет ну чтобы не поми пацаны
It's just not that there wo
Это же просто
n't be such a question How much
не просто не будет такого вопроса лько
money has been invested in this project, just
денег вложено в этот проект просто
so much money has been invested in this project Well,
столько денег вложено в этот проект Да
Trump will just say now look  [ __ ]
ну просто Трамп сейчас скажет смотри суч
not money the essence of life Yes why
не деньги суть жизни Да зачем дальше
invest money in the project further it is better to
вкладывать деньги в проект лучше
fix it and save the lives of the guys Well, that's it,
зафиксировать и сохранить жизни ребят Ну
fix it and
вот именно зафиксировать и всё и
save the lives of the guys give
сохранить жизни ребят отдать Украине
Donetsk Lugansk back to Ukraine
назад Донецк Луганск всё
everything everything Even in Ukraine itself there is a kind of
всё Даже на самой Украине рису типа
map where there is no Odessa region,
карты уже где нету ни Одесской области
no Zaporozhye, no Sons Well, you understand
ни запорожска ни сонс Да ну ты понимаешь
that there are females there and Zelensky he is a
что по самки их там а Зеленский он
puppet of nationalists they will not
марионетка националистов они ему не
let him draw such maps in short they will
дадут короче такие карты нарисовать они
say everything Either we wipe the
будут говорить всё Либо мы стираем с
Donetsk Lugansk region off the face of the earth
лица земли донецкую луганскую область
or they give it to us Well Well, and how with what they
либо её Нам отдают Ну Ну а чем чем они
will wipe it out Well, like with drones whatever you want you
сотрут Ну как все дронами чем хочешь ты
understand they will not let us live already well
же понимаешь они не дадут жить уже ну
this is again a war like it will drag on again there will be more and more
это опять война типа затянется опять
people will die
дальше будут дальше будут люди погибать
right It is better that they do not die it is
правильно Так лучше чтобы не погибали
better that Russia gives Donetsk Lugansk
лучше чтобы Россия отдала Донецк Луганск
back to Ukraine everything will never be given never
назад Украине всё никогда не дадут
given Well, it turns out
никогда не отдаст Ну так вот получается
Putin does not want peace
Путин не хочет мира
yes and here people do not even want to be with Ukraine you
да а здесь люди даже не хотят с Украиной
understand How many people died
уже быть понимаешь Сколько людей погибло
look look the point is not that Yes they want or do not
смотри смотри суть не в том Да хотят не
want it is very simple Putin says we  we
хотят очень просто Путин говорит мы
give Crimea and Donetsk Lugansk
отдаём Крым и Донецк луганс
at go he says Look who wants to
у го он говорит Смотри кто кто хочет
go to Russia goes to Russia you
уехать в Россию уезжает в Россию вы
go to Russia and that's it Who wants to
уезжаете в Россию и всё Кто хочет
stay with Ukraine stays with
оставаться с Украиной остаётся с
Ukraine everything is
Украиной всё
clear it will be the same as in the current year it will be that
чётко будет то же самое как в шем году
one to one it will be the same that the
будет что вот один в один будет то же
same it will be like in the
самое что то же самое будет как в
fourteenth year what well what was in the fourteenth
четырнадцатом году что ну что было в
year And what in the fourteenth
четырнадцатом году А что в четырнадцатом
year So if Russia does not help
году Так если Россия не будет помогать
everything in 2-3 days everything will end Well I
всё через 2-3 дня всё закончится Ну я те
tell you the miners will become and go to fight
говорю станут шахтёры и пойдут воевать
than if Russia takes the troops and
чем если Россия заберёт войска и и
equipment it will never take the equipment
технику не заберёт никогда технику
look Ukraine will launch a couple of airstrikes and that's it
смотри Украина нанесёт пару авиаударов и
in short and everyone will run away Well Russia will
всё короче и какие все разбегутся Ну не
never take the equipment like
заберёт Россия никогда типа технику
Russia is retreating yes Russia is retreating and immediately
Россия отходит да Россия отходит и сразу
all these militants who were with
все вот эти боевики что вались вместе с
Russia are leaving and that's it and clear and all
Россией сваливают и всё и чётко а все
who lived peacefully remain to
кто мирно жил остаются
live Someday even the peaceful will take and
жить Некогда даже мирные возьмут о и
will fight Well look in Kherson  now you
будут воевать Ну смотри в Херсоне сейчас
understand even peaceful people now
понимаешь даже у мирных людей сейчас
have weapons that they will take and
есть оружие которое возьмут типа и будут
fight like well what kind of
воевать типа ну какое вот у тея утебя
weapons do you have there will be a need for Well you see
есть оружие там надо будет Ну вот видишь
you don't have any And what will you do take
у тебя нету И ты что сделаешь возьмёшь
Well there are two steps for me like what will happen And
Ну там мне два шага ти типа будет что И
what if you are not full now Well if you have
что если ты сейчас не пол Ну если ты
n't gone to defend since
сейчас не пошёл защищать с
2014 you haven't gone to defend
четырнадцатого года ты не пошёл защищать
Lugansk then you won't go now I'll go won't
Луганск то и теперь не пойдёшь
go since you haven't
пойду не пойдёшь раз ты уж сейчас не
gone now they won't take yet and they won't take they won't take
пошёл не берут пока а не берут не берут
Until yes yes Understand Well and then they won't take you
Пока да да Поня Ну и потом не возьмут
see and it will turn out that they will take Well well
видишь и получится так возьмут Да ну
just like with Kherson Russia
просто так же как с херсоном Россия
said that Kherson is already Russia
сказала что Херсон - это уже Россия
then ran away threw
потом убежала кинула
everyone didn't offend retreated because it
всех не обижала отступила потому что
was tactically important Well so it is
тактически важно было Ну вот и так
tactically important to retreat for example
тактически важно отступить например
Lugansk and
Луганска и
Crimea Well this is just insanity
Крыма Ну это маразм просто
then to Russia It's boring to point a finger at
будет потом в Россию Бут тыкать пальцем
why Russia left
ного нудно по что Россия ушла
raised its hands  and Anya ran for Kharkov
подняла ручки и убежала Ани за Харьков
until now Russia fingered what what
до сих пор России пальцем-то
for
что что за
Kharkov Well when in Kharkov in the
Харьков Ну когда в Харькове в
Kharkov
Харьковской
region were Russian troops and then
области были росийские войска и потом
retreated Well look now Russia can't
отошли Ну вот смотри теперь Россия не
even win back the Kursk region
может отвоевать даже курскую область Да
Well if we exchange the Kursk region for the
вот если разменять курскую область на
Luhansk region if they
луганскую
can't win
если не смогут
back
отвоевать
from the EU for six months they can't even win
от ЕС уже полгода даже больше не могут
strategy strategy people are smart they sit like they
стратегия стратегия люди умны сидят типа
think there
думают там
Generals for a reason they have
Генералы не зря уних по
such Ugh passport
такие Уй паспорт
remained Well of course no one takes it
остался Ну конечно его никто не забирает
seriously Well of
серьёзно Ну
course That is you have both a Russian passport
конечно То есть у тебя и паспорт России
LNR passport and a Ukrainian passport
паспорт лнр и паспорт Украины
there it's cool That is in principle you
там прикольно То есть в принципе ты
when this what
когда
when Ukraine comes you take out your
когда Украина придёт ты достанешь
passport and say I am a
паспорт и скажешь я
citizen no
гражданин нет
Yes no I said Russian cart weapons
Да нет я же сказал руский воз оружие
buvo your own I understood who your wife
буво своё понял кем у тебя жена
works as a nobody And who do you
работает никем А ты кем
work as
работаешь
doesn't matter
неважно
Yes secret information You are a real secret like
Да секре информация Ты прямо секрет
that Listen here's how you are with
тако Слушай вот как ты с
my language
мово
Yes and Alexey Mo yes who was the field
Да а Алексей Мо да кто был полевой
commander Well I think these Luhansk
командир Ну я считаю это Луганские
ones were standing there honestly I don't remember the
эти там стояли там честного не помню
last name
фамилию
egov I killed him
егова Убил его
I  I think that the n government
Я считаю что нское правительство
What kind of
Какое
Lugansk Plotnitsky people yes
луганс плотницкого люди да
yes it just turns out that I see that
да просто получается что я смотрю что
all these heroes of Donbass yes All somewhere
все вот эти герои Донбасса да Все где-то
somehow died them somehow their own to remove
как-то погибли их как-то свои поубирать
but Yes I know that many of their own And can I
ан Да я знаю что много своих А можно я
watch What do you have a wife yes Can
смотрел Что у вас вот жена есть да Можно
I let her answer me let her not
я пусть она мне ответит пусть она не
go into the frame but I'm just interested in
заходит в кадр но просто вот интересно с
talking to her she hears me World Cup
ней поговорить она меня слышит ЧМ
no I think maybe Give me one earphone I
нет Я дума может Дайте один наушник Я
want to ask her a couple of questions it's also
хочу ей пару вопросов задать тоже
interesting I've never talked to girls from Lugansk
интересно я с девушками с Луганска
how she
никогда не общался как вот она жизнь
sees life Give me one earphone and
видит Дайте один наушник и
one do you want to talk don't say that I'm from
один хочешь пообщаться не скажи что я из
Khmelnitsky Yes I'm interested to hear
Хмельницкого Да мне интересно услышать
her opinion about from Khmelnitsky wants to
её мнение о из Хмельницкого хочет
hear your opinion where From Khmelnitsky
услышать твоё мнение откуда С Хмельницка
and what opinion I'm busy Well tell me I want
и что мнение Я занята Ну скажите Я хочу
I don't
я не
communicate Tell her not to show her face yet
общаюсь Скажите чтобы лицо она не пока
just
просто
go I'm a blogger she's a TikTok blogger
пого я блогер она тиктокерский блогер
tell me I don't show her just I'll
скажите Я с не не показывает просто
talk Well she doesn't want to talk she doesn't
поговорю Ну не хочет о разговаривать не
want to understand Well she's so arrogant Yes she's a
хочет понял Ну она такая гонорова Да она
TikTok blogger yes yes in  tiktok sells
tiktok блогер да да в тиктоке продаёт
something through tiktok who sells something
что-то через tiktok кого продаёт что-то
through
через
tiktok don't sit there something clicks I don't
tiktok не сиди там что-то клацает не
know I understood what to sell what to sell
знаю понял что продавать то что
ki to buy something Why are you
продавать ки на что-то купить Что вы ко
pestering me communicate to yourself I don't
мне прицепились общайтесь себе Я не
communicate
общаюсь
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
Tue Poti
Вт Поти
she doesn't laugh Well I
она не хохочет Ну
understood how much you've already drunk today a lot a lot a
понял сколько ты уже сегодня
lot - that's how much I don't know I did
много много много - это сколько Не знаю
n't count Well
не считал Ну
approximately well a normal person would have already
приблизительно ну нормальный человек уже
fallen well really How much did you drink who How much did you
упал бы ну реально Сколько выпил кого
drink today there Well yes I'm a
Сколько выпил сегодня там Ну да я же
normal person I would have fallen and died I
нормаль человек же упал бы и умер бы
understood
понял
yes And what do you think for example who is to
да А как ты считаешь например кто
blame for the fact that
виноват в том что
uh Yanukovych fled to Russia and not to
ээ Янукович убежал в Россию а не в
Lugansk and
Луганск и
Donetsk Yanukovych And why if
Донецк Янукович А почему вот если
uh you were all there Donetsk Lugansk and in
ээ вы были все там Донецке Луганске и в
Donetsk Lugansk Why did he flee to
Донецке Луганске Почему Он убежал в
Russia
Россию
That is, he didn't trust you Donetsk and
То есть он не доверял вам донецким и
Lugansk
луганским
Yes so in Donetsk he pressed
Да такн в Донецк прижал
at all he didn't press at all Like in my opinion if
вообще вобще не прижал Типа помоему если
I'm not
я не
mistaken and didn't press  pressed several
ошибаюсь а не прижал прижал несколько
times Well, also
раз
very rarely
Ну тоже там очень редко
pressed And now it turns out where his parents
прижал А сейчас получается его родители
live I dont know Well, his parents oh Trump
живут не знаю ну родители его ой трампа
Yanukovychs words Well, I dont
гово Януковича Ну я не
know They were already hidden
знаю они и так скрыты были
there
там
Shes visible
виде она
I know where the wife and children are There the children
Я же знаю где жена и дети там дети
say those went the son
говорят те пошёл сын
drowned either or will drown or not drown and
утонул то ли то ли утонут то не утонут и
then Tana covered in darkness yes yes For
потом Тана покрытая мраком да да Для
everyone there in Russia no one even
всех там в России даже никто не
knows I understood Listen, how do you
знает понял Слушай а как вот ты
estimate How long will the war go on
оцениваешь Сколько ещё будет идти война
I think for a long time very long that
это я думаю долго очень долго
is Lugansk boys will still
то есть Луганские пацаны будут до сих
die
пор умирать
Yes, everyone will die Well, Lugansk I You are
Да все будут умирать Ну лугански я Ты же
from Lugansk I feel
из Луганска вот мне луганских
sorry for Lugansk Lugansk Donetsk and Russian
жалко Луганский Донецкий и российский
Ukrainian do you want to fight to the
украински вы хотите воевать до
last Lugansk residents
последнего луганчане
Well, we dont call anyone up now Yes
Ну у нас сейчас никого не призывают Да
because the EU Voit is long to call up the
потому что ЕС Войт долгот призывать
last one
последнего
we had once at
у нас один раз был при один
once Are you ready to fight to the last
раз Вы готовы воевать до последнего
Lugansk residents
луганчане
yes And why do you need the Earth then Without Lugansk residents
да А зачем вам тогда Земля Без луганчане
Dashas children will be like this if you are
Даши детям будет так если вас не
gone What kind of
останется Какие ваши
children are you, come back  to Ukraine Live children
дети вернитесь в Украину Живите детей
note No Now only like this A Ask or
ноте Нет Теперь только так а Спроси или
wife of the same opinion
жена такого же мнени
she will
она по-другому
say differently ask her she will not have the
скаже это вот спроси у не она не будет
same opinion this is
такого же мнения это
for sure My wife is from Western Ukraine where we
однозначно У меня жена Западной Украины
went from there we were discharged from there to
откуда ездили выписывали оттуда
send
отправлять
doi send I will go myself when it will be
дой отправ я сама поеду когда будет
normal there you
нормально там
negotiate now she is different zat Come on let's
договариваешь сейчас она по-другому зат
talk to her tell her
Давай е сюда мы поговорим с ней скажи
that I really want to
что я очень хочу с ней
talk to her ho tell her tell her that
поговорить хо передай передай скажи что
I really ask her to change
я очень прошу е пере
girlfriends Well ask her what she
подружки А ну спросите у не как она
thinks if Putin gives Lugansk to
считает если Путин отдаст луганску
Ukraine what will happen
Украине что будет Вот
Ask her what you think if Putin gives
спросите как думаешь если Путин отдаст
Hans to Ukraine what
Ганс Украине что
will happen will not give And
будет будет не отдаст А
why does no one want it in Ukraine no one
почему нем в укра
wants in Russia no one asks the
хочет в России никто не спрашивает
opinion of the people Yes Putin will say to give it to
мнение народа Да Путин скажет отдать
Ukraine then you will not go to a
Украине значит вы же не выйдете на
rally against
митинг против
Putin here people will simply take up arms and
Путина здесь просто народ возьмёт оружие
go
пойдёт
to fight many that you are simply in a trap you
воевать мно что просто ты себя в лове
can't even listen Give one Give
даже не можешь слуша Дайте один Дайте
just one earphone to your wife just
просто один наушник жене просто
one does not want to talk talk about so
один не хоче общаться гово по
many weapons
стоко много оружи
what  There will be no desire here at all
что Желания здесь вообще не будет
completely Ukraine will no longer be Pooh and No
полностью Украины уже не будет Пух и Нет
all Lugansk will go and seize
уже все Луганские пойдут и захватят
Ukraine Yes so many
Украину Да столько
weapons Well some are such that there will be no
оружия Ну какие-то стоят такие что не
Ukraine missiles What missiles do you have
бут Украины ракеты Какие ракеты у вас
what missiles do you have there in
какие ракеты у вас там стоят в
Lugansk it doesn't matter This
Луганске неважно Это уже
will already be information Ukraine but Russia
информации будет Укра но Россия эти
will take these missiles back will
ракеты заберёт назад
never take them back not for a long time I understand they take a
не заберёт никогда ни долго едут понима
very long time to get there the movement is very
очень долго едут уних жение очень
small does not matter ketas koto Masha
маленькое не значе кеты кото Маши
the speed is very
скорость очень
low and when will
маленькая а когда будет
something be personnel And
что-то личный состав А
not tanks of the Armed Forces such such throws
не танки ВС такое такое кидает
were whales Personnel composition was
были киты Лич состав был
VN you can even read there is VM
ВН можешь прочитать даже есть ВМ
access Understand In short
доступе Поня Короче
why are you so de
ты почему
missiles Lugansk And so on in the fable
де ракеты Луганские И так дальше же
hazelnut tree at
басне орешник у
hazelnut tree I did not say that z hazelnut street
орешник Я не сказал что з орешники стрит
Nara information I looked by the way here is what
Нара информацию Я смотрел кстати вот что
you have this carpenter and with him there
у вас вот это плотницкий да и с ним куча
were a bunch of corruption scandals what are they
была коррупционных скандалов что они там
stealing there Only Lugansk grannies it's
разворовывают Только бабки Луганские это
true yes it was like that And why don't you
правда да было таком А почему вы не
change him for
поменяете его на
another one  changed to
другого е поменяли на
who who now at us the head of the inskaya region
кого кто сечас у на глава инской области
Lord Forgot
Господи Забыл
who would cook porridge
да кто
I have a cough but
каше я не могу завари У меня кашель же
toycha arranged
тойча обставил
[music]
[музыка]
like Shilin in Donetsk And we have who and you have
как Шилин в Донецке А у нас ктон а у вас
who I myself forgot we are degrading Well who is the
кто Я сам забыл деградируем Ну кто у вас
head of your
глава
Republic your I forgot his last
Республики ваши Я его забыла
name now in short they laugh at us
фамилию сейчас короче ржут с нас
yeah
ага
forgot but now you don't perform anywhere
забыл та сейчас нигде не выступаете
put I forgot attention question on so
поставили Я забыл внимание вопрос на
you have about a minute time has gone we
таки у вас есть о минута время пошло
discuss more know than so that you found out
обсуждаем больше зна чем так что ты
forgot I voted for him us
забыл я за него голосовала
forgot what are
ус забыла как
our last names
фамили нас
now hasn't changed so 30 seconds left
сейчас не менялся так 30 секунд осталось
know so let's let's be
зна таки давайте давайте
generated
генерируются
[music]
[музыка]
and we are degrading so Dear experts
а мы деградируем так Уважаемые знатоки
attention question last name k heads the
внимание вопрос фамилия к возглавляет
Lugansk People's Republic for whom are you
луганскую народную Республику за кого вы
voting then Putin and
Голосова то Путина и
all the voting choice Who will answer
всё голосовани выбо Кто будет отвечать
from your
от вашей
team never went to the elections so
команды ходил никогда на выборы так
your wife will answer So Tell her
отвечать будет ваша жена Итак Скажите ей
let her give an answer What is the last name of the hall on
пусть она даёт ответ Как фамилия хол на
elections what did you find out not Oh wait
выборы что ты узнал не Ой подожди
So you went to the elections wait now
Так ты ходил на выборы подожди сейчас
Lord I forgot his last name Yes I know We
Господи я забыла фамилию его Да зна Мы
open the first letter The first letter P
открываем первую букву Первая буква П
Petr Pasechnik I said on
Пётр Пасечник Я же сказала на
p wait then she hears me
п подожди то она меня слышит
You listen you hear him Well a little I'm
Ты слышь ты его слышишь Ну чуть-чуть я
in the earphone he's shouting there and then you gave
же В наушнике он там кричит а то вы дали
her headphones or not your own headphones And
ей наушники ли не у не свои наушники А
how does she hear
как она слышит тогда
me then like that Pasechnik Cool yes don't
меня таком рить Пасечник Прикольно да не
shout please got it Okay Listen
кричите пожалуйста понял Хорошо Слушайте
Well you did it you did it anyway
Ну вы справились вы справились на таки
super
супер
young Leonid Pasechnik That was a very important
молод Леонид Пасечник Это был очень лый
question For whom Golosova in the elections but
вопрос За кого Голосова на выборах но
in short she did it she did it
она короче справилась она
And can you tell me in what let's say
А можете сказать в чём скажем правление
Pasechnik's rule is better than
пасечника лучше правление
Plotnitsky's rule Well at least he doesn't steal So how does
плотницкого Ну хоть не ворует Так а как
he
он
steal Well everyone
ворует Ну все
steals you understand put any person in charge
воруют понимаешь любого человека поставь
Well and he hasn't been knocked for
ти Ну и он е пока не был стука за
this yet well how yes the fact that Zelensky himself is a
этим ну как да то что самый Зеленский
thief like openly Like everyone is silent
вору типа в открытую Типа все же молчат
everyone likes it fine  it's all the
всем прекрасно нравится это всё так как
same here somewhere maybe GTO something And we are silent
же где-то может ГТО что-то А мы молчим
Because because what Because you
Потому
can't talk like
что Потому что нельзя говорить как
you can't talk What is forbidden in Russia to
нельзя у вас Что запрещено в России
talk Well
разговаривать
how can you not tell Zelensky you
Ну как ты же не скажешь зеленскому ты
steal so much look Zelensky
столько много воруешь смотри Зеленский
you steal so much I can say
ты столько много воруешь я могу сказать
nothing will happen to me for this Well you
мне ничего за это не будет Ну ты там
can say something like in your office now And
сейчас можешь сказать своём кабинете
so go out openly to people Like
типа А так выйти в открытую людям
Why is our president so many and
сказать Типа Почему наш президент мно и
so anyone can say anything
так можно кто угодно может говорить У
We have everything in Ukraine somehow calmly
нас что угодно в Украине как-то спокойно
with
с
this And what in Russia can't you say that
этим А что в России нельзя сказать что
someone is
там кто-то
stealing Well who will listen to
ворует Ну кто будет слушать
Tito everything And what will they do with someone who goes out and says
Тито всё А что сделают с тем кто выйдет
something against the President in Russia
и что-то против Президента в России
Odena let's
одена давай так
rephrase it like this the person
перефразирует бутылки будет у человека
who says something against the government in
который скажет что-то против власти в
Russia will not have bottles Why does the diameter of the bottle
России не будет Почему диаметр бутылки
mean you can talk Yes against the government in
значит можно говорить Да против власти у
your country
вас
Well how if you have rallies like
Ну как если вы с митингами типа что
against Putin like
против Путина типа
yes the police will find out firstly like
да милиция узнать во-первых типа
sanctioned you are
санкционировано вас
not this firstly
нет это во-первых
like the reason why you
типа причину почему вы так
decided so well then further
решили ну там уже дальше
locally  power like Listen, but you
местно власть типа Слушай а вот ты же
lived, I wonder, you lived under Ukraine Do you
жил вот интересно ты жил при Украине Ты
remember how rallies were held in Ukraine, you did
же помнишь как в Украине проводились
nt need permission, you just
митинги не нужно было разрешение просто
submitted an application that there would be a rally and you
подавалась заявка что будет митинг и
could rally no Yes, no, you had to, thats
можно было митинговать не Да нет надо
how We went out When I
во я Ну как Мы выходили Когда я
worked
работал саль
here, they didnt pay us salaries, so we
Здесь нам не платили зарплаты вот
went out to a
выходили на
rally, the same thing, people pressed their shoulder straps
митинг тоже самое жали люди погона
One to one, everything is the same, nothing has
Один в один всё то же самое ничего не
changed absolutely again, look, I
поменялось абсолютно ещё раз смотри я в
also conducted and held rallies in Ukraine, it
Украине проводил тоже и проводил митинги
turns out that you simply submit an application that there will be a
получается ты просто даёшь заявку что
rally, an oriented
будет митинг ориентированное
number Stop This is not a permit, it simply
количество Стоп Это не разрешение просто
notifies that there will be a rally so that the
уведомляет что будет митинг для того
police can guard this territory
чтобы полиция охраняла эту территорию
so that there are no some kind of time yes, yes, but
чтобы не было каких-то ка время да да но
this is not the case in Russia, you need to
это это не раз в России нужно
say it incorrectly in Russia In Russia, you need to
неправильно сказал в Рос в России нужно
get permission until you are given
получить разрешение пока тебе не дали
permission, you cannot hold a rally
разрешение ты митинг не можешь проводить
in Ukraine You simply submit an application that you
в Украине Ты просто даёшь заявку что
are holding a rally and thats it, and you
проводишь митинг и всё и проводишь
only hold it, like, what are you, you again
только какую типа что ты ты опять-таки
write, like, what kind of rally are you holding there, in connection
пишешь типа какую ты там митинг в связи
with which are you holding, in connection with which  Yes, if the
с чем ты проводишь в связи с чем Да если
state wants What it considers that it is
государство хочет Что считает что там
impossible to hold a rally there for some
нельзя провести митинг из каких-то
reasons, then it goes to court and
соображений оно тогда в суд обращается и
only by a court decision can they
только судебным решением могут
restrict
ограничить
Well, well, this is basically the same as in
Ну ну это в принципе то же самое как и в
Ukraine Yes, there is little What is the difference
Украине Да там мало Чем отличается ещё
again In Ukraine there are no permits for rallies
раз в Украине нет разрешений на митинги
In Ukraine you hold a rally you just gave an
в Украине ты проводишь митинг просто дал
application that you have a notification not an application
заявку что у тебя уведомление не заявку
But a notification That you are holding and that's it and you
А уведомление Что проводишь и всё и
hold it But in Russia until you get
проводишь А в России пока ты не получишь
permission you have me I say you
разрешение у тебя ми я те говорю ты
submit an application you can't even approve it no no no
подаёшь заявку тея те даже одобрить её
in Ukraine In Ukraine there is no approval of
нет нет нет в Украине в Украине нет
applications for rallies in Ukraine
одобрения заявок на митинги в Украине
not once look in Ukraine there is no
нераз е раз смотри в Украине не
permit system in Ukraine
разрешительная система в Украине
notification system Yes, you just notify the
уведомительная Да ты просто уведомляет
rally and that's it and hold it
митинг и всё и проводишь
Thank you I'm sitting
Спасибо я сижу
[music]
[музыка]
Okay, let it be
Ну ладно пускай будет
So it didn't shock me now you sing for 5 seconds
так так не потрясло сечас поёшь 5 секунд
and I was shocked come on That's it
а мне потрясло давай
I'm in
Всё я на
place Damn, you're so
месте Блин ты так
shish with the microphone so rustle with the microphone What's
шиш микрофоном так шурши микрофоном Что
crazy In the sense of a microphone microphone
жесть В смысле микрофона микрофон
headphones Well, like
наушников Ну типа
somewhere
где-то
y te
й те
give Listen and what do you think Putin is
даю Слушай а как ты считаешь вот Путин
already old when he dies who should
уже старенький когда он умрёт кто должен
rule
править
Russia But what president Well who do
Россией Но президент какой Ну кто кого
you see as
ты видишь
president yet I don't see anyone Well
президентом пока никого не вижу Ну вот
yes Putin will die who to put in place of Putin
да Путин умрёт кого вместо Путина
but he will choose will put I don't
поставить а вот выберет поставит Я не
know Well who Whom Well honestly I don't know like
знаю Ну кого Кого Ну чесно не знаю типа
tomorrow imagine Putin will have a heart attack
вот завтра представляешь Путина инфаркт
everything tomorrow Trump everything Yes that's who to
всё завтра Трамп все Да вот кого вместо
put in place of Putin in Russia
Путина бегом ставить в России
Zhirinovsky has also already died who to
Жириновский тоже уже помер кого ставить
put in place I don't know Well he has like a deputy Putin has no deputy he goes now everything is frozen the battery ran out that's how all these Lugansk like pipsqueak comment subscribe to my Telegram right now ovin and popk very and very important YouTube Zaga us through scarg or in your ban and very many
через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже багато
videos I don't show people at times I don't show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams That's why so that
информация про стрими Тому для того щоб
we Mali  operational link is written
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
right now and while there in telegram okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм
video there is also interesting and useful information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we will oblige you with trima constant
и мы повинни з вами трима постийний
operational link
оперативный звязок
independently in that che will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
write M
пиши M